Mss.B.F865
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, 1855; 6-1/2x4; Agassiz, Louis, 1807-1873
    [1855]. A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Agassiz, no. 11.) formerly B F865.a. Asks for subscriptions for his forthcoming work. On same sheet as broadside: Agassiz. Private Circular...; May 28, 1855. Film 1249
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, 1855; 10-3/4x8-1/4; Meigs, Charles D., (Charles Delucena), 1792-1869
    Thursday evening [ca.]. A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Jan. 14, 1856; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Feb. 1, 1856; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Is ill. Concerning the APS. Refers to Fairman Rogers. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, March 2, 1856; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Cambridge, A.L.S.with initials. 1p.and add. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, March 30, 1856; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, May 16, 1856; 10x7; Agassiz, Louis, 1807-1873
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Agassiz, no. 12.) Formerly B F865.a. Friendly letter. Concerning the walrus. Concerning scientific needs. Film 1249
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], June 17, 1856; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, June 21, 1856; 10x8; Kirkwood, Daniel, 1814-1895
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870. Astronomical and geological matters.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Philadelphia, July 21, 1856; 10x8; Smithsonian Institution.
    Washington, L.S.: Joseph Henry. 1p. Contains figuring in pencil. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Henry, no. 12.). Formerly B F865.h. Asks him to examine paper on chemistry. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, July 23, 1856; 10x7-3/4; Kirkwood, Daniel, 1814-1895
    Newark, Del., A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Astronomical and geological matters.
  - Letter to John Fries Frazer, July 27, 1856; Bache, A.D., (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Friendly letter. (See Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.)
    Formerly B F865.b. Film 1249.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Aug. 3, 1856; 10-1/2x8-1/4; Hall, James
    Albany, A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks him to deliver a speech at the meeting of geologists. Refers to A.D. Bache.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Aug. 4, 1856; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Albany, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to the American association for the advancement of science. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Aug. 13, 1856; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878
    A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Henry, no. 13.) Formerly B F865.h. Concerning the chemistry paper he is to examine. Concerning "Henry Darwin Rogers." Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Aug. 15, 1856; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Business. Refers to Henry and the American association for the advancement of science. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Aug. 15, 1856; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Henry, no. 14.) Formerly B F865.h. Asks for the manuscript on chemistry. Film 1249.
  - Letter to John [Fries] Frazer, Philadelphia, Aug. 18, 1856; 8x5; Hilgard, J. E. (Julius Erasmus), 1825-1891
    New York, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks that report be sent to Bache in Albany.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Sept. 5, 1856; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to Agassiz and Hare. Film 1249.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Oct. 2, 1856; 8x5-1/4; Duane, William J. (William John), 1780-1865
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks for money for political purposes.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Nov. 22, 1856; 8x5; Gould, Benjamin Apthorp, 1824-1896
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Special dinner for a few from the American association of science.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Nov. 26, 1856; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning his lectures to be delivered to the Mercantile library. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Dec. 8, 1856; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Dec. 10, 1856; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Dec. 21, 1856; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Dec. 31, 1856; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer;], Nov., 1857; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to the APS. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Feb. 19, 1857; 8x4-3/4; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D. Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. A. D. Bache to Frazer, 27 July 1856. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Feb. 21, 1857; 8x4-3/4; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, March 8, 1857; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to J.K.Kane. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], March 18, 1857; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], March 18, 1857; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], March 24, 1857; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning a sample of sand. Refers to Trego and the American association for the advancement of science. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], March 24, 1857; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Makes a request. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], March 25, 1857; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, June 11, 1857; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], June 15, 1857; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to LeConte. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, June 17, 1857; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to LeConte. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, July 2, 1857; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], July 9, 1857; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Aug. 27, 1857; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache) Formerly B F865.b. Business. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Philadelphia, Sept. 10, 1857; 8x5; Peirce, Benjamin, 1809-1880
    A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Refers to F.Rogers.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Sept. 17, 1857; 8x5-1/2; Brown-Séquard, Charles-Edouard, 1817-1894
    Paris, A.L.S. 2p. Enc. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Will not teach at Cooper union. For enclosure, see: Brown-Séquard to P.Cooper; [Sept. 1857].
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Nov. 2, 1857; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Nov. 15, 1857; 7-3/4x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    New York, A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Dec. 2, 1857; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Dec. 22, 1857; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn Fries] Frazer, Dec. 25, 1857; 7-1/2x5; Orr, Hector
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning various subjects. Concerning lectures at the Franklin institute.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Jan. 3, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to the APS. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Jan. 6, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Jan. 19, 1858; 7x4-1/4; Kane, John K., (John Kintzing), 1795-1858
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks for help in making coastal survey report.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Jan. 20, 1858; 10x7-3/4; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to Jo[h]n F[ries] Frazer, Jan. 22, 1858; 7-1/2x4-3/4; Orr, Hector
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Sends publication.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Jan. 25, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning H.D. Gilpin. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to John [Fries] Frazer, Jan. 28, 1858; 6-1/2x4; Agassiz, Louis, 1807-1873
    Cambridgte, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Agassiz, no. 13.) Formerly B F865.a. Friendly letter. Film 1249
  - Letter to John [Fries] Frazer, Feb. 3, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Agassiz, Louis, 1807-1873
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Agassiz, no. 14.) Formerly B F865.a. Friendly letter. Film 1249
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Feb. 22, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Feb. 24, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Philadelphia, March 6, 1858; 8x5-1/4; Hoepper, Adolph S.
    Lancaster, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Refers to Lesley.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], March 22, 1858; 9-3/4x8; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D. Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], April 22, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], April 26, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], May 30, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to Humboldt. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, June 10, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], July 4, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Philadelphia, July 28, 1858; 9-1/2x7-1/2; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    New York, A.L.S.with initials. 1p.and add. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D. Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Sends guano to the university for examination. Film 1249.
  - Letter to John [Fries] Frazer, Philadelphia, July 29, 1858; 9-3/4x8; Hilgard, J. E. (Julius Erasmus), 1825-1891
    Washington, 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Refers to A.D.Bache.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Aug. 20, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Agassiz, Louis, 1807-1873
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Agassiz, no. 15.) Formerly B F865.a. Friendly letter. Introduces Th[omas] E. Clerk. Film 1249
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Sept. 6, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Peirce, Benjamin, 1809-1880
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Introduces Judge Peat who is interested in eduction.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Sept. 15, 1858; 8x5; Gould, Benjamin Apthorp, 1824-1896
    Albany, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Refers to A.D.Bache.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Sept. 19, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to Rothrock and Agassiz. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Oct. 9, 1858; 7x4-1/2; Schaeffer, Charles Frederick, 1807-1879
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 2p. (see-Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Business.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Oct. 11, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S.with initials. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to Hassler. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Oct. 15, 1858; 10x7-3/4; Schaeffer, George C.
    Washington, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Need of abstracts of foreign items in Franklin institute journal.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Oct. 16, 1858; 10x8; Henry, Joseph, 1797-1878
    A.L.S. 3p.and enc.wanting. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Henry, no. 15.) Formerly B F865.h. Forwards letter by Schaeffer and asks help for him. Friendly letter. Attached to this is letter from Schaeffer to Frazer; Nov. 26, 1858. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Nov. 2, 1858; 8x5; Peirce, Benjamin, 1809-1880
    A.L.S. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter. Sends toasts.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Nov. 8, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    New York, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Will visit them soon. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Nov. 17, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Nov. 18, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Nov. 26, 1858; 10x8; Schaeffer, George C.
    Washington, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from Henry. no. 15.) Formerly B F865.h. Thanks for offer of aid. Attached to letter from Henry to Frazer; Oct. 16, 1858. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Dec. 1, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letter from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to the university of Pennsylvania. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Dec. 5, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 2p.and 1p.of figuring. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to the APS. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Dec. 7, 1858; 7-1/2x5; Cook, Asher, Jr.
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 10p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning his illness.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Dec. 11, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Concerning lectures. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Dec. 15, 1858; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Concerning the APS and Fraley. Film 1249.
  - Receipt to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Dec. 18, 1858; 8x5; Harding, John (?)
    Philadelphia, A.D.S. 1p. (see Frazer Papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.)
  - Letter to J[ohn Fries] Frazer, Dec. 18, 1858; 8x5; Hayes, I. I, (Isaac Israel), 1832-1881
    A.L.S. 2p. Enc.wanting. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning his proposed expedition.
  - Note to [John Fries Frazer, March, 1858?; 5x7-3/4; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.N.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D. Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. A. D. Bache to Frazer, 27 July 1856. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Jan. 9, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning an article by Frazer. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Jan. 10, 1859; 8x5; Hilgard, J. E. (Julius Erasmus), 1825-1891
    Washington, A.L.S.2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks that he check some proofs for the American association. Refers to Kane.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Jan. 12, 1859; 8x5; Gould, Benjamin Apthorp, 1824-1896
    Albany, A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Jan. 18, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to the APS, Agassiz and Fraley. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Jan. 26, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 4p. (see Frazer papers. Letter from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Business. Concerning the University of Pennsylvania, Agassiz and F.Rogers. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Jan. 31, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, Feb. 11, 1859; 7-1/2x7; Espy, James P., (James Pollard), 1785-1860
    Washington, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Asks report on his paper on meterology
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, March 16, 1859; 8x5; Gould, Benjamin Apthorp, 1824-1896
    Albany A.L.S. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], March 25, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Business. Refers to the university of Pennsylvania. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], March 26, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. University of Pennsylvania business. Refers to Agassiz. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], April 2, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. Enc.of newspapers clipping in Latin. (see Frazer papers. Letters from University of A.D. Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. University of Pennsylvania business. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], April 5, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to A[lexander] D[allas] Bache, April 6, 1859; 10x8; Saxton, Joseph, 1799-1873
    Washington, L. 1p. Copy. Enc.of 2p.of printed matter. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning the production of screws.
  - Resolution, May 17, 1859; 7x5; University of Pennsylvania. Trustees
    D. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning Frazer(?).
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], May 24, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. University of Pennsylvania business. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], May 31, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], June 6, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Concerning Agassiz. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], June 10, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    Washington, A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to LeConte and Rogers. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], June 27, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Philadelphia, July 8, 1859; 8x5 and 12-3/4x7-3/4; Gilliss, J. M. (James Melville), 1811-1865
    Washington, A.L.S. 2p.and enc.of 12p. Copy. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence..., 1834-1870.) Astronomical problems.
  - Letter to [John Fries] Frazer, July 20, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S.with initials. 3p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Concerning Persifor Frazer. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], July 29, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], July 30, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Newport, Aug. 16, 1859; 10x7-3/4; Murray, John B.
    New York, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Business.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Aug. 19, 1859; 9-3/4x7-3/4; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    New York, A.L.S.with initials. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D. Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Film 1249.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Aug. 31, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Concerning Persifor. Film 1249.
  - Letter to J[ohn] F[ries] Frazer, Sept. 8, 1859; 8x5; Barnes, Albert, 1798-1870
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence ...; 1834-1870.) University of Pennsylvania business.
  - Letter to [John Fries Frazer], Oct. 9, 1859; 8x5; Bache, A. D. (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867
    New York, A.L.S.with initials. 2p. (see Frazer papers. Letters from A.D.Bache.) Formerly B F865.b. Friendly letter. Refers to Agassiz. Film 1249.
  - Letter to John F[ries] Frazer, Oct. 24, 1859; 9-1/2x7-1/2; Bassett, Ebenezer D., 1833-1908
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Frazer papers. Correspondence...; 1834-1870.) Concerning an invention by Ruhmkorff.